<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on oseniabdulhaleem</title>
    <link>https://oseniabdulhaleem.pages.dev/categories/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on oseniabdulhaleem</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://oseniabdulhaleem.pages.dev/categories/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Turning rejection into opportunities</title>
      <link>https://oseniabdulhaleem.pages.dev/post/2024-01-30-turning-rejection-into-opportunities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oseniabdulhaleem.pages.dev/post/2024-01-30-turning-rejection-into-opportunities/</guid>
      <description>The Power of Positivity As humans, finding positivity in every situation we face can have profound effects on our well-being.&#xA;Encountering rejection, whether in professional pursuits or personal aspirations, can be a challenging experience. However, looking on the bright side and identifying areas for improvement can significantly contribute to personal growth.&#xA;Turning Setbacks into Stepping Stones Every rejection, if approached with a positive mindset, can play a pivotal role in refining one&amp;rsquo;s skills and character.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Shipping and Logistics using from an investors perspective here in nigeria</title>
      <link>https://oseniabdulhaleem.pages.dev/post/2024-01-02-global-shipping-and-logistics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oseniabdulhaleem.pages.dev/post/2024-01-02-global-shipping-and-logistics/</guid>
      <description>logistics services in nigeria&#xA;asos/amazon/ali express logistics services in nigeria&#xA;logistics that do inter state delivery from food/clothe how jumia is doing and how individual business are also handling it with local logistics company&#xA;skynet logistics company used by asos&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m fascinated by the global shipping industries from how the global food supply chain relies on it to how our daily life necessities is delivered through it.&#xA;The shipping industry is extremely big the amount of import and export that goes through the ocean is astronomical and a disruption in a particular route and can have a major impact on all the trade(link ryan peterson video)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why i used JSON token as a authorisation mechanism</title>
      <link>https://oseniabdulhaleem.pages.dev/post/2024-01-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oseniabdulhaleem.pages.dev/post/2024-01-15/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Importance of verifying hash on the server side during authentication</title>
      <link>https://oseniabdulhaleem.pages.dev/post/06-01-2024-importance-of-verifying-hash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oseniabdulhaleem.pages.dev/post/06-01-2024-importance-of-verifying-hash/</guid>
      <description>Overview User authentication is a critical aspect of web applications, ensuring that only legitimate users gain access to protected resources. When integrating third-party authentication systems, such as the Telegram Login Widget, it becomes crucial to validate the received data on the server side. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll delve into the process of hash verification and its significance in maintaining the security of your web application.&#xA;Authentication with Telegram Login Widget In the context of my web application, I chose to leverage the Telegram Login Widget for user authentication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warehouse Scale Computing</title>
      <link>https://oseniabdulhaleem.pages.dev/post/2024-01-02-warehose-scale-computing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oseniabdulhaleem.pages.dev/post/2024-01-02-warehose-scale-computing/</guid>
      <description>I remember during my Industrial Training programme in school where I was introduced to the world of networking. I did my Industrial training at Network operations center of my school an institution that provides internet services over 3000 concurrent users</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Example Post</title>
      <link>https://oseniabdulhaleem.pages.dev/post/2024-03-09-usecallback-hook-coming-to-the-rescue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oseniabdulhaleem.pages.dev/post/2024-03-09-usecallback-hook-coming-to-the-rescue/</guid>
      <description>I was recently faced with a challenge to update a button payment reference on success and failure and this was how react useCallback hook came to the rescue&#xA;// import { PaystackConsumer } from &amp;lsquo;react-paystack&amp;rsquo;;&#xA;// export default function PaystackButton() { // // Generate initial config with a function to ensure dynamic reference updates. // const config = { amount: 1000 }; // const getUpdatedConfig = () =&amp;gt; ({ // email: &amp;lsquo;intelrail@gmail.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
